tutorial9.net 2010-06-12

# Privacy Policy | Tutorial9

## Tutorial9.net Privacy Policy

The privacy of our visitors to Tutorial9.net is important to us.

At Tutorial9.net, we recognize that privacy of your personal information is important. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you use visit Tutorial9.net, and how we safeguard your information. **We never sell your personal information to third parties.**

### Log Files

As with most other websites, we collect and use the data contained in log files. The information in the log files include your IP (internet protocol) address, your ISP (internet service provider, such as AOL or Shaw Cable), the browser you used to visit our site (such as Internet Explorer or Firefox), the time you visited our site and which pages you visited throughout our site.

### Cookies and Web Beacons

We do use cookies to store information, such as your personal preferences when you visit our site. This may allow us to keep you logged into special site features such as our Forums, or automatically fill in data for you in various forms.

We also use third party advertisements on Tutorial9.net to support our site. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP , the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

You can chose to disable or selectively turn off our cookies or third-party cookies in your browser settings, or by managing preferences in programs such as Norton Internet Security. However, this can affect how you are able to interact with our site as well as other websites. This could include the inability to login to services or programs, such as logging into forums or accounts.

### Links

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Tutorial9.net is not responsible for the privacy practices, or content of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this website.

#### Free Goodies. Delivered to You.

Subscribe to Tutorial9, and we'll deliver you the newest freebies and tutorials for free.

**Subscribe By Email**

**Subscribe By RSS**

Write for Us

#### Write for Tutorial9

  * Do you want to get paid $150 for writing at Tutorial9?
  * Are you a talented Photoshopper, Blogger, or Photographer?
  * Want to help thousands of others by sharing your knowledge?

If so, we're interested in you, and we'll pay you. Find out [how to write](http://www.tutorial9.net/get-paid-to-write/) for Tutorial9.
